Guide to the Bob and Gennie DeWeese papers1946-2007
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
Bob and Gennie DeWeese papers
1946-2007
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
DeWeese, Robert, 1920-1990; DeWeese, Gennie, 1921-2007
2640
24 linear feet 55 boxes
Personal files and artwork of Bob and Gennie DeWeese, two Bozeman-based artists and teachers who helped to build Montana's modernist art scene.
Collection is open for research
Gift of Tina DeWeese on behalf of the DeWeese Family, 2018 and 2019.
Divided into the following series: 1. Bob DeWeese-Biographical Files, 2. Bob DeWeese--Working Files, 3. Bob DeWeese--Correspondence, 4. Gennie DeWeese--Biographical Files, 5. Gennie DeWeese--Working Files, 6. Gennie and Bob DeWeese Gallery, and 7. DeWeese Web Archive
Robert (Bob) and Genevieve (Gennie) DeWeese were pioneers in the modernist movement in the state of Montana. Primarily painters and printmakers, both artists influenced a generation of students through their teaching and involvement with the Montana arts community. Bob was Professor of Art at Montana State University from 1949 to 1977. Prior to that, he taught classes at Texas Tech University and Ohio State University. He earned his B.S. from Ohio State University and his M.F.A. from University of Iowa in 1948. In 1946 he married Gennie, who was a fellow art student at Ohio State.
They had five children together: Cathie, Jan, Gretchen, Tina and Josh. According to Tina, "Art was certainly their common ground, but family is what held them together." Both were also committed to "equal studio time"; Tina has observed that "Gennie was a feminist before the word was known."
Both Bob and Gennie exhibited extensively throughout the state and major retrospectives of their works were presented at the Montana State University School of Art (1979) and the Yellowstone Art Center (1991) for Bob, and at the Missoula Art Museum (1996) for Gennie. In 1995 Bob and Gennie received the Montana Governor's Award for the Arts. That same year, Gennie was awarded an Honorary Doctorate of Fine Arts from Montana State University in Bozeman.
Bob and Gennie were a hub for a very lively community of intellectual, modernist thinkers and artists of their generation, mostly a cross section of university faculty. They loved to stay in touch with what people were thinking about and what was new in their respective fields through hosting parties which provided them with lifetime friends. Bob DeWeese passed away in 1990, and Gennie in 2007. The DeWeese children continue to honor their parents' life work.
Prior to its donation to MSU, the collection was held by the DeWeese Family, who donated it in multiple accessions between 2018 and 2019.
The collection focuses on the professional work and personal lives of both Bob and Gennie DeWeese, including sketches of commissioned artwork (murals for Bob, book illustrations for Gennie). It has examples of art done by both, such as illustrations done by Gennie DeWeese for the book Hamlet's Planets, items related to the Bob and Gennie DeWeese Gallery, and exhibitions such as Robert DeWeese, a Retrospective.
Also within the collection is correspondence with other Montana artists such as Jerry Rankin, Jessie Wilber and Frances Senska, reflecting the DeWeese's extensive social and professional network with creatives of significane in twentieth century Montana.
The collection also has a large variety of exhibit catalogs and flyers for the Yellowstone Art Museum and the Missoula Art Museum, among others. In addition to examples of his artwork, the collection also has items from Bob DeWeese's career as an art professor at Montana State College (now Montana State University).
The first donation included a box of materials about Gennie DeWeese collected by Terry Karson, which was separated into its own collection.
Montana State University--Bozeman--Faculty
Montana
Artists--Montana
Fine Arts; Montana
Works of art; Biography; Artist files; Correspondence; Web archives; Biographies
- Bob DeWeese biographical files, 1946-1990; 1; 4 linear feet
  This series includes correspondence, teaching materials, notes and student papers. Series one is divided among 2 sub-series, personal and education/teaching.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Personal, 1946-1990; 1; 0.4 linear feet
    Personal papers and items of Bob DeWeese such as his resume and Army papers.
    - Army papers, 1946-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Birth certificate copy, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Handwritten resume, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Healthcare notes and questionnaire, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Identification cards, 1971-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Job searches, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Lona E. DeWeese estate, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Passport, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Pocket address book (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Provisional Special Certificate, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Veterans Administration papers, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
    - Bob's Memorial, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Educational and Teaching, 1946-1977; 2; 3.5 linear feet
    Two types of papers are represented in this subseries: Papers related to Bob DeWeese's time as a student, and papers related to his tenure as a professor at Montana State Collage, including lesson plans, student work, and administration records.
    - Italian Renaissance class notes, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Italian Renaissance class notes, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Italian Renaissance class notes and reports, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Oriental Art class notes and reports, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Oriental Art class notes and reports, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Oriental Art class notes and reports, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Oriental Art class notes and reports, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 20th Century Art class report, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Class notes, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Class notes, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Esthetic-Modern-Medieval notes, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Exams, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Northern Renaissance class notes, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Northern Renaissance class notes and reports, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Northern Renaissance class notes and reports, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Shakespeare's Comedies class notes, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Program for Master's Degree, January 21, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Medieval Art/Northern Renaissance class notes, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Thesis, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Thesis, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Class report (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Ohio State University notebook, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Texas Tech University class and scheduling records, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Texas Tech University ceramics notebook, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Montana State College contracts, 1949-1964 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Art 225, Life Drawing, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Supply lists, 1952-1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Notes, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Notes, Life Drawing, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Student art exhibition catalogs, 1956-1971 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - The Word, 1957 Spring (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Notes, Drawing, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Notes, Art 119 - Drawing, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Notes, Watercolor, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Notes, Art 119, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Notes, Art 119 - Drawing, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Notes, Art Appreciation, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Prospect, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Notes, Art Appreciation, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - School of Architecture sketching program, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Teaching materials, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Notes, Watercolor, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Notes, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - College of Graduate Studies, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Faculty documents, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Individual annual report, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Life Anatomy, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Life Anatomy, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Retirement contributions, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - 19th Century Impressionism, January 1965 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Montana State University contracts, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - "Contemporary Art 321 - Samples of tests, papers, journals", 1966 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - "Contemporary Art 321 - Samples of tests, papers, journals", 1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Art 321 - Contemporary Art, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - "Contemporary Art 321-Sherman's Cézanne", 1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "Department", 1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Cézanne and Visual Form teaching materials, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Cézanne and Visual Form teaching materials, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Cézanne and Visual Form teaching materials, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Hoyt L. Sherman correspondence, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Student journals, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - "Department politics", 1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Art 321 final exams, 1967 March 17 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Guest artists, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Graduate faculty materials, 1970-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Student papers, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Notes, Art 111, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Notes, Art 111, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - MSU School of Art Faculty Exhibition catalogs, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Notes, Art 114, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Notes, Art 111, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Preliminary class rolls, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Notes, Art 111, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Notes, Art 114 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Notes, Art 205 - Painting (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Notes, Art 218 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Notes, Art 118 - Drawing (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Notes, Drawing (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Notes, Oil Painting, Freshman Drawing, and Water Color Painting (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Notes (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - "Prints School" (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Readings, "Gassett Mimes Wisdom" (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Readings, "General Art Mimes Wisdom" (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Readings, "Intaglio Mimes Wisdom" (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Student journal (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Student journals (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Syllabus drafts (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Mary Lou, Michael-Bob Shimabukuro Letters (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Quotations-Notes-Ideas", 1951-1960 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Painting, Drawing, and Art Appreciation (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Perspective, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Resumes (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Dog tags (Box 30, Item 2)
    - Paintbrushes (Box 30, Item 3)
    - Robert DeWeese Studio stamp (Box 30, Item 4)
    - Piccolo (Box 30, Item 5)
    - Belt (Box 30, Item 6)
    - Painted letter to P.D. Skaar (on woodblock) (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Montana State University Professor Emeritus certificate (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Montana State University Professor Emeritus resolution, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Bob DeWeese working files, 2; 13 linear feet
  Series 2 contains art projects and materials, notes, newspaper clippings, correspondence and photographs.
  This series is divided between four subseries: projects, exhibitions, filing cabinets and documentary ephemera.
  - Projects, 1; 2.9 linear feet
    Includes material related to workshops, murals, graphic projects)
    Arranged by project.
    - Examples of Work, 1940-1948 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Buckley Field Program Designs, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Winter Fair Barns, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Winter Fair Proposal for Mural-Photos, Bozeman Public Library, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Winter Fair Mural Documents: Drawings, Photos (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Bank Mural Preliminary Sketches (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Bank Mural, 1960, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Quake Lake Mural, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Collage Scraps/Xerox (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Proposed Murals and photos-Mural and Architecture proposals (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Montana Cultural Congress newsletters, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Cadenza, Montana Music Educators Association magazine, 1962-1967 (Box 10, Folder 2-5)
    - DeWeese Children's Papers and Drawings, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Rimer, Rhode Island Music Educators Association magazine, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Richard Hugo Poem (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - John Buck and Deborah Butterfield - "John and Debbie" (Box 10, Folder 9-11)
    - Buck Butterfield-Clippings, brochures, photos (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Jessie Wilber and Frances Senska: Correspondence, newspaper clippings, postcards, 1952-2006 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
    - Personal letters to and from other artists, 1944-1990 (Box 11, Folder 4-6)
      Much of the correspondence is from Lou Penfield.
    - Les Barret Drawings and Photographs, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Jerry Rankin, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - James Reineking - Correspondence, art brochures, photos, 1969-2000 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - David Dunlap, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Ben Tone, Hamada, Leach, 1982-2005 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Neil Parsons, 1964-1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Bill Stockton, "Today I Baled Some Hay to Feed the Sheep the Coyotes Eat" manuscript (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Bill Stockton, 1971-2007 (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
    - Art - Cadenza, 1947-1967 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Cadenza, 1962-1967 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings, sketch of dog, and art gallery letter, 1960-1964 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Art Sketches and Studies, 1942-1952 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - George Conky Sculpture Questionnaire, 1961-1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - School of Art, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Art Institute Class Trip, notes, 1972-1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Hospital Memorial Memorabilia, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Notes from Friends and Gallery Flyers, 1956-1986 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - "De Kooning Problem" Lecture Slides, 1977 January (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Collected Art from Magazines and Print (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Dirk Lee to Gennie DeWeese, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Catalog of the School of the Art Institute of Chicago, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Writing, Teaching notes, Shows, etc., 1972-1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Order Books - Auction Sales (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
  - Exhibitions, 2; 3.3 linear feet
    Includes art lists and prices, notes and correspondence with galleries, gallery announcements
    - Notes - "Our Abode Almost a House We (Almost) Built in Texas Before Jessie Called from Bozeman", 1949 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Notes and Correspondence - Includes poem "Memories of a DeWeese Proof" by John D. Flemming, 1972-1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Notes and To-Do Lists (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Notebook - Art Inventory (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Bob DeWeese Auction - Photos, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Bob DeWeese Auction - Item list and sales, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Bob DeWeese Retrospective, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Robert DeWeese Exhibition, 1991 August 30 (Box 55, Vhs 1)
    - Rabbit Book Baltimore (photo album), 1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Old Trailer Inventory Notebook (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Postcards and exhibition memorabilia, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Notebook - "Slides (Tina)" (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Bob DeWeese Appraisal reports, 1998, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Bob DeWeese Appraisal reports, 1998, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
    - YOKOI: "The Legacy of Robert DeWeese", 1991 Winter (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Bob DeWeese Appraisals, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - DeWeese Appraisals by Dennis Kern (Box 55, Floppy-disk 1)
    - Fine Art Appraisals (Draft), 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Bob and Gennie Shows, 1978-2006 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
    - Personal Bob Memorabilia, 1951-1992 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
    - Bob Memorabilia, 1974-1987 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Letters of Condolence to Gennie DeWeese, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Writings about Bob, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - P.D. Skaar; Auction Correspondence, 1977-1981, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Printing Schedule and Prep for Bob DeWeese Print Show, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
    - Exhibition Flyers and Invitations, 1982-2007 (Box 17, Folder 6-10)
    - Exhibition Flyers and Invitations, 1973-2007 (Box 18, Folder 1-6)
    - Exhibition Flyers and Invitations, 1964-2007 (Box 19, Folder 1-7)
    - Exhibition Flyers and Invitations, 1987-2007 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
    - Exhibition Flyers and Invitations, 1979 (Box 54, Box 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1983-1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Billing Lists for Northcutt Gallery and Auction, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Current Art: Show and Grant Applications, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Publicity, 1985-1999 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Mary Lou - Michael Bob Shimabukuro Columns, Tina Letters, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Gen. Newspaper Stuff; Lou Reed Article, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Recent Letters and Recommendations", 1981-1986 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
    - Trips and Others' Art, 1982-1985 (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
    - EMC and Advertising, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Filing Cabinet, 3; 6 boxes
    Files taken from a filing cabinet kept by Bob DeWeese, includes drafts of projects, artwork, correspondence, and documents relating to shows and workshops that Bob participated in. The materials give insight into his working process and what items he kept over the years.
    While some items were refoldered, they kept their original labels, and their original order as arranged by Bob DeWeese; labels may not exactly adhere to contents)
    - DeWeese Art Stuff, 1962-1988 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Newsweek, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Art Memorabilia, 1977-1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Auction Lists and Prices, 1979-1985 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - CAA-Boston, Letters, etc., 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Letters to Editor, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Chicago, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Big Fork Gallery, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - CAA and Danto Reviews, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Announcements, 1980-1987 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Resumes, 1979-1987 (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
    - Resumes, loan, and auction receipts, 1983-1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Art Shows, price lists, etc., 1987-1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Artist Resource Bank (ARB) Update, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Washing Project for the Arts, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Gallery Paule Anglim, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - DeWeese Catalog - Price lists, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Yellowstone Art Center - Record of Acquisition, University of Washington - Lynn Basa Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Montana Draw Exhibition, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Robert DeWeese Work since 1949 - Price List, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Introduction by Rudy Autio and Foreword by Dennis O'Leary for Exhibition Catalog (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts (AVA), 1983-1988 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Art for the Aged, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Art Correspondence, 1959-1987 (Box 23, Folder 12-13)
    - Letters about My Shows, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Paris drawings and reproductions, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - "Shows" Calendar of Paris sketches, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Press and Publicity, 1961-1985 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Rapture Article, Ariel Horoscope, Studio Essays, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Shows, 1954-1989 (Box 24, Folder 3-8)
    - Workshops, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Yellowstone Art Center, 1981-1990 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - House Plans and Kid's Drawings, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Essays, Exhibitions, 1960-1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Exhibitions, 1941-1985 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Various Letters, 1961-1963 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Letters to MSU Faculty and Students, Retirement Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - MSU Classes - Enrollment and correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Art Piece Orders, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Stuff from Studio Tack Wall, 1975-1978 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Artwork from Studio Tack Wall (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Basic Art Courses, Old Department Stuff, 1945-1965 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Painting 405, 1975 Fall (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Documentary Ephemera, 4; 9 boxes
    This series contains examples of Bob's work, such as a portfolio of sketches.
    - Miscellaneous realia (necklace, medal, mini chalkboard, etc.) (Box 29)
    - Tie wrapped in green tissue paper (Box 30, Item 1)
    - Sign: "So, how much money is art worth?" (Box 30, Item 7)
    - Painted cloth swatches (Box 30, Item 8)
    - Small pieces of art by Bob DeWeese, photographs, newspaper clippings, and Xeroxes (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
    - Assorted notes, sketches, newspaper clippings, sketches and photos (Box 31, Folder 4-8)
    - Photographs (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Random posters, correspondence (Some OS) (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Posters for gallery and show announcements (auction of Bob's work after his death in 1986, a performance that Jan DeWeese was in) (Some OS) (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Documentary ephemera related to Bob's work/process? (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - GB DeWeese Gallery poster mock-ups, calendars (OS) (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Folder of Xeroxed material (photographs, Bob sketches, etc.) (OS) (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Paintings on canvas board (Bob?) (OS) (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Calendars, 1983-1984 (OS) (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - "Kids' Drawings of Bob" -- Portraits of Bob DeWeese by Butte Fifth and Sixth graders during a workshop for the Butte Public Schools, sometime in 1981 (OS) (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Charcoal (?) sketch on paper, "Paris E.A. Ariel" (can't read additional writing) (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Photograph of Tina DeWeese (?) on horse (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Portfolio (Containing documentary ephemera (miscellaneous photographs, scraps of paper, sketches, bits of writing, fabric printed with woodcuts)) (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Donald Gilbert Wood's BFA thesis from The Ohio State University, 1948 [Teaching Materials] (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Matisse Folder of reproductions of various famous artworks (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Reproductions of famous artworks (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Reproductions of famous artworks (Box 8, Folder 3-7)
    - Reproductions of famous artworks (Box 26, Folder 6-7)
    - Press, 1956-1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Art Pamphlets and Publications (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Art Pamphlets and Publications (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - German and Italian Artists - Prints and Reproductions, 1953-1961 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Mounted Reproductions (Box 27, Folder 3-6)
    - Time Magazine Art Sections, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - De Kooning Reviews and works by other artists, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Art Reproductions: Nude Drawings (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Postcards and Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition and Gallery Pamphlets, 1950-1965 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Workshops with Young Children and Students (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Cardboard Signs: "International Child Art" and "In the MSC Art Dept. Collection of Original Works of Art" (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Art Postcards, 1950s-1960s (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Shows and Exhibitions (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1948-1964 (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
    - Miles City Art Show - Bob and Gennie, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Exhibition Stuff (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Bob DeWeese correspondence, 3; 5 boxes
  Correspondence contains letters, condolence notes and newspaper clippings. (note that this series is not exhaustive and that other correspondence may be found interspersed throughout the rest of the collection)
  This series has no formal arrangement